 --> --> Design Automation Home Solutions Enterprise Content Management Eval Educational Solution Suite OMR Exam Software Computer Based Test Platform Learning Management Solution Question &amp; Test Management Bank On-Screen Marking Platform Print Product Engineering Custom Product Engineering Design and Artwork Automation Resources About Contact Careers Blogs --> Home Solutions Enterprise Content Management Eval Educational Solution Suite OMR Exam Software Computer Based Test Platform Learning Management Solution Question &amp; Test Management Bank On-Screen Marking Platform Print Product Engineering Custom Product Engineering Design and Artwork Automation Resources About Contact Careers Blogs Tip: Try searching for “Mixologyst” or “Handyman”. --> Home Solutions Enterprise Content Management Eval Educational Solution Suite EVAL EXAMS OMR Exam Software Computer Based Test Platform Learning Management Solution Question & Test Management Bank On-Screen Marking Platform Print Product Engineering Custom Product Engineering Design and Artwork Automation Resources --> About Contact Careers Blogs Home Solutions Enterprise Content Management Eval Educational Solution Suite OMR Exam Software Computer Based Test Platform Learning Management Solution Question & Test Management Bank On-Screen Marking Platform Print Product Engineering Custom Product Engineering Design and Artwork Automation Resources --> About Contact Careers Blogs $(window).on('scroll', function(e){ if( $(".dropdown-menu").hasClass('show')){ $(".dropdown-menu").removeClass('show'); } }); Design Automation Reduce significant time and effort in designing artwork and manage design processes using automation Book a Demo You can now automate the artwork design process with Vir Softech's custom plugins of desktop and digital publishing to create high quality artwork with 100% accuracy. You get it all at a much lower time, money, and review effort. When compared to the current manual process, our automation has resulted in a nearly 75% reduction in time for designing artwork. Design and Artwork Automation Traditional artwork creation for packaging workflow is often based on digital publishing apps such as InDesign, CorelDraw, Photoshop, Acrobat, Illustrator etc features For regulated industries, such as pharma and consumer durables, there is a need to customize the product packaging to cover the regulatory aspects of countries where the product is being sold. As a product owner, you may now need to design multiple versions of product designs for folding box, blisters, packets, leaflets and a variety of packages. This is complex, error-prone and costly. With Vir Softech’s custom plugins you can now automate the artwork design process to create high quality artwork with 100% accuracy. And, you all get this with far reduced investment in time, cost, and review effort. One of the global pharma companies uses our custom InDesign plug-in to automate the designing of leaflets and folding boxes for various medicine brands. The customization includes features such as automated placement of content such as text, images and tables, multi-column alignment, multi-language support, font style and paragraph style application, blank space adjustment. Actually the list goes on and on, and can be customized to your needs. Our automation has resulted in almost 75% reduction in time for designing of a leaflet as compared to the current manual process. Custom Plugins Various desktop publishing software such as InDesign, CorelDraw, Photoshop, Acrobat, Illustrator have advanced digital publishing. While these have powerful features, they lack many workflow advancements that digital publishers need. Publishers need to manage and enhance PDF workflows, optimize web documents for printing and optimize content for various market segments. We develop plug-ins in C++, scripts, VBA, VSTA & HTML for Windows and Mac OS. Our specialization is across industrial segments such as print, imaging, graphics, and publishing. We have done scripting models for: Workflow automation and optimization Web to print solutions Variable data printing InDesign Server integration Some of our recent work includes: Help customers replace Flash based extensions with CEP HTML based plugins Improve printing and packaging workflows, with variable data printing Improve color management and imposition Incorporate 3D visualization and CAD functionality Create powerful UI components using wxWidgets that integrates with SDK See Case Studies --> Testimonials Lorem ipsum dolor Photographer, INDIA " Sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco. " Loreium ipsum Loreium ipsum Lorem ipsum dolor Photographer, INDIA " Sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco. " Loreium ipsum Loreium ipsum Lorem ipsum dolor Photographer, INDIA " Sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco. " Loreium ipsum Loreium ipsum --> Clients Ut enim ad minim veniam Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Labore et dolore magna aliqua Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum --> Book A Demo Today Our introductory consultation call includes: A discussion to collect your key business requirements A demo of the product/solution by our Product Manager Advice on the next steps to get your project moving --> if ( window.history.replaceState ) { window.history.replaceState( null, null, window.location.href ); } function callSweetMsg(){ swal({ title: "Error!", text: "Here's my error message!", type: "error", confirmButtonText: "Cool" }); } 64 && event.charCode 96 && event.charCode Quick Links Home About Contact Blogs Careers Solutions Enterprise Content Management (ECM) EVAL Solution Suite Computer Based Tests (CBT) Optical Mark Reader (OMR) Learning Management System (LMS) Question & Test Bank (QTB) Online Screen Marking (OSM) Design Automation Product Engineering (Print) Contact Us corp@virsoftech.com 18005717711 0120 - 4325 497 9319086751 USA Sales Office aruna@virsoftech.com +1 (408) 839-7063 Connect With Us © Vir Softech Pvt Ltd | All Rights Reserved | 2022 Quick Links Home Resources About Contact Blogs Careers Policies Solutions Enterprise Content Management (ECM) EVAL Solution Suite Computer Based Tests (CBT) Optical Mark Reader (OMR) Learning Management System (LMS) Question & Test Bank (QTB) Online Screen Marking (OSM) Design Automation Product Engineering (Print) Contact Us corp@virsoftech.com 987 125 8989 0120 - 4325 497 987 125 8989 987 125 8989 Connect With Us © Vir Softech Pvt Ltd | All Rights Reserved | 2021 --> --> $(document).ready(function () { $("#myBtnContainer").on("click",'.filter_btn', function () { var $this = $(this); // if we click the active tab, do nothing if (!$this.hasClass("active")) { $(".filter_btn").removeClass("active"); $this.addClass("active"); // set the active tab // get the data-rel value from selected tab and set as filter var $filter = $this.data("rel"); //// if we select view all, return to initial settings and show all if ($filter == 'data-all'){ $(".filterDiv") .not(":visible") .show() } else { // otherwise var all = $(".filterDiv"), active = all.filter(function () { var $datalist = $(this).data("filter").split("|"); return $.inArray($filter, $datalist) > -1; }) all.not(active).hide(); active.show(); } } }); }); function onlyNumberKey(evt) { // Only ASCII character in that range allowed var ASCIICode = (evt.which) ? evt.which : evt.keyCode if (ASCIICode > 31 && (ASCIICode 57)) return false; return true; } 
