 --> --> Product Engineering Services Home Solutions Enterprise Content Management Eval Educational Solution Suite EVAL EXAMS OMR Exam Software Computer Based Test Platform Learning Management Solution Question & Test Management Bank On-Screen Marking Platform Print Product Engineering Custom Product Engineering Design and Artwork Automation Resources --> About Contact Careers Blogs Home Solutions Enterprise Content Management Eval Educational Solution Suite OMR Exam Software Computer Based Test Platform Learning Management Solution Question & Test Management Bank On-Screen Marking Platform Print Product Engineering Custom Product Engineering Design and Artwork Automation Resources --> About Contact Careers Blogs $(window).on('scroll', function(e){ if( $(".dropdown-menu").hasClass('show')){ $(".dropdown-menu").removeClass('show'); } }); Home Solutions Enterprise Content Management Eval Educational Solution Suite OMR Exam Software Computer Based Test Platform Learning Management Solution Question &amp; Test Management Bank On-Screen Marking Platform Print Product Engineering Custom Product Engineering Design and Artwork Automation Resources About Contact Careers Blogs --> Home Solutions Enterprise Content Management Eval Educational Solution Suite OMR Exam Software Computer Based Test Platform Learning Management Solution Question &amp; Test Management Bank On-Screen Marking Platform Print Product Engineering Custom Product Engineering Design and Artwork Automation Resources About Contact Careers Blogs Tip: Try searching for “Mixologyst” or “Handyman”. --> Product Engineering Services Your go-to partner for IT-led process transformation for product life-cycle management, development or workflow optimization needs, with a special focus on print Book a Demo Print Products In today's dynamic economy, print and publishing companies must rapidly introduce new products and features to gain competitive advantage. The expected speed of change puts massive pressure on internal R&D teams to address fast high priority customer reported issues. Vir Softech is the ideal value added software service provider for print and publishing companies that need to move quickly without sacrificing quality while maintaining a profit margin. We assist customers in enhancing their business by providing high-quality software services at affordable prices, whether they are developing new software products, enhancing existing products, or supporting legacy products. At Vir Softech, we have a world-class team of computer scientists with decades of experience in managing all aspects of Imaging technologies and replacing RIP technologies with comparable/improved performance and quality. Why should you trust us? Proven experience in print areas such as RIP, color management, job management &amp; settings, printer &amp; cutter workflows, half-toning, VDP, imposition, bands generation and advanced functions such as nesting, tiling, step &amp; repeat, and so on. We help you target RFPs for specific market segments, such as production, industrial, commercial, large format and enterprise printing. Having enagement with print OEMs across geographies lsuch as Japan, USA, Europe you can trust us to proide across production, enterprise, graphic cards and large format printing segments. Why OEMs and ODMs choose us for RIP Replacement Services About 100 person years of combined print technology and domain experience Super-strong expertise on PostScript, PDF, PCL & XPS Experience of working across enterprise, production and large format printers Member of Global Graphics software Partner Network - Implementation partner for Harlequin & Mako Hands-on experience of working on all the major RIP technologies available in market including Harlequin RIP, Adobe RIP and GhostScript Comprehensive training &amp; consulting support Experience of developing PDF applications using 3rd party PDF libraries Expertise in developing Plug-ins for Adobe - Illustrator, InDesign, Acrobat, Photoshop & CorelDraw Track record of successfully working with multiple print OEMs worldwide See Case Studies --> Custom Services With Vir Softech engineering services you can offload your end-to-end software development for business-leading transformation in managing documents, optimizing education, bringing new age printing services, or workflow management of artwork and design in print and packaging setups. You can rely on us to meet all of your current and future engineering and technology needs. You can work with us in multiple models – you can outsource your engineering needs at a solution-level, module-level, or skill-level. New Product Development Product ideation, conceptualization Prototyping Beta testing &amp; go-to-market Product Transformation Legacy transformation and regular upgrades Technology assessment & migration Mobile Cloud SaaS enablement Maintenance &amp; Testing Life-cycle management Product enhancements Product maintenance &amp; testing UI/UX development Visual design and asset creation Front-end engineering HTML/CSS Wireframes Concept prototype Programming Languages C, C++, Java C# PDLs - PostScript, PDF, XPS HTML5, JavaScript, JSP, HTTP, REST, J2EE, Node.js Oracle, PostgreSQL NoSQL DB - Mongo DB ReactJS, Angular, Google Flutter Operating System Platform Linux - RHEL, CentOS Monta Vista, WindRiver microITRON ThreadX (ARM) Windows/Mac Cloud platforms - AWS, Azure Domains Print & Publishing workflows Production/Enterprise Printing/Grphic Arts/Large Format Digitization workflows Plug-ins for Acrobat, Indesign, Illustrator, Corel Draw Print Drivers - Win (V3/V4 architecture) and Mac See Case Studies --> Clients Freehand Graphics Mutoh RISO Roland Stage3 Tech Mahindra Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum Lorem ipsum --> Book A Demo Today Our introductory consultation call includes: A discussion to collect your key business requirements A demo of the product/solution by our Product Manager Advice on the next steps to get your project moving --> if ( window.history.replaceState ) { window.history.replaceState( null, null, window.location.href ); } function callSweetMsg(){ swal({ title: "Error!", text: "Here's my error message!", type: "error", confirmButtonText: "Cool" }); } 64 && event.charCode 96 && event.charCode Quick Links Home About Contact Blogs Careers Solutions Enterprise Content Management (ECM) EVAL Solution Suite Computer Based Tests (CBT) Optical Mark Reader (OMR) Learning Management System (LMS) Question & Test Bank (QTB) Online Screen Marking (OSM) Design Automation Product Engineering (Print) Contact Us corp@virsoftech.com 18005717711 0120 - 4325 497 9319086751 USA Sales Office aruna@virsoftech.com +1 (408) 839-7063 Connect With Us © Vir Softech Pvt Ltd | All Rights Reserved | 2022 Quick Links Home Resources About Contact Blogs Careers Policies Solutions Enterprise Content Management (ECM) EVAL Solution Suite Computer Based Tests (CBT) Optical Mark Reader (OMR) Learning Management System (LMS) Question & Test Bank (QTB) Online Screen Marking (OSM) Design Automation Product Engineering (Print) Contact Us corp@virsoftech.com 987 125 8989 0120 - 4325 497 987 125 8989 987 125 8989 Connect With Us © Vir Softech Pvt Ltd | All Rights Reserved | 2021 --> --> $(document).ready(function () { $("#myBtnContainer").on("click",'.filter_btn', function () { var $this = $(this); // if we click the active tab, do nothing if (!$this.hasClass("active")) { $(".filter_btn").removeClass("active"); $this.addClass("active"); // set the active tab // get the data-rel value from selected tab and set as filter var $filter = $this.data("rel"); //// if we select view all, return to initial settings and show all if ($filter == 'data-all'){ $(".filterDiv") .not(":visible") .show() } else { // otherwise var all = $(".filterDiv"), active = all.filter(function () { var $datalist = $(this).data("filter").split("|"); return $.inArray($filter, $datalist) > -1; }) all.not(active).hide(); active.show(); } } }); }); function onlyNumberKey(evt) { // Only ASCII character in that range allowed var ASCIICode = (evt.which) ? evt.which : evt.keyCode if (ASCIICode > 31 && (ASCIICode 57)) return false; return true; } 
